# **VAISHAK V K**

□ vaishakhvkv@gmail.com

( +91 7639644554/ +91 9007095554

https://github.com/VaishakVk/

## **PROFILE**

3 years of experience as a developer and consultant of Software Applications using Oracle Applications R12 and Oracle Fusion. Excellent knowledge on **SQL, Python, Javascript** and **PLSQL**. Keen on working on challenging projects and contribute to make a good product.

## **KEY SKILLS**

• SQL, Python, Node JS, PLSQLL, MongoDB, Git, Mongoose, Git, HTML, CSS, Javascript

#### **PROJECTS**

# **Car Rental App**

Deployed - <a href="https://vk-car-rental-app.herokuapp.com">https://vk-car-rental-app.herokuapp.com</a>
Source Code - <a href="https://github.com/VaishakVk/CarRentalBooking">https://github.com/VaishakVk/CarRentalBooking</a>

- Developed the backend for a car rental application.
- Contains logic for session creation, authentication and authorization.
- Built on Node JS using Express library
- Database setup using MongoDB
- Admin routes setup for creation of multiple entities
- Coupon Validation feature setup.

## **Auction API**

Deployed - <a href="http://vk-auction-boh.herokuapp.com">http://vk-auction-boh.herokuapp.com</a>
Source Code - <a href="https://github.com/VaishakVk/Auction-BoH">https://github.com/VaishakVk/Auction-BoH</a>

- Developed REST API for an auction website.
- Contains logic for authentication and authorization.
- Powered by Node JS, Express and Mongo DB
- Email notification send to winners after successful completion of Auction by using CRON jobs

## **Blockchain LoC**

- Development of REST API for LoC Approval
- Node JS and Express server.
- MongoDB Database connection.
- LoC Email notification to be sent to supplier.

## **WORK EXPERIENCE**

KPMG Global Services (Associate Consultant) Feb- 2017 – Oct 2017 KPMG Global Services (Consultant) Oct- 2018 – Present

- Oracle Fusion Technical Consultant
- Development of Blockchain backend application using Node JS.
- SOA and ICS developer
- Developed several PLSQL packages
- Write complex and efficient SQL queries

## IBM India Pvt. Ltd. (Application Developer) Jun- 2015 – Feb 2017

- Oracle EBS Developer of Integrations and Conversion objects.
- Oracle EBS Technical Developer
- Analyzing the failures for the daily batches by checking the session logs.
- Automating daily job status report along with errors using Python.
- Performance tuning of several packages and SQL queries.

## RECOGNITIONS

- Super Team 2018 Q3 Cycle Awarded for excellent delivery throughout the project duration
- Kudos 2018 Q2 Cycle Awarded for high delivery quality of the integrations
- Manager's Choice Award 2016 Awarded for practicing the quality Keep the client first
- Deep Skill Adder Award 2016 Q4 Cycle

## **EDUCATION**

Course	Institution	Year of Completion	Marks % / CGPA
B.E	PSG College of Technology	2015	8.81
XII	S.B.O.A Matric. Higher Secondary School	2011	97.83
X	S.B.O.A Matric. Higher Secondary School	2009	92.2